<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anna Hanna Sarah</title>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anna Hanna Sarah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First COS19 Project </title>
      <link>http://example.com/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t wait what it will be about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 4</title>
      <link>http://example.com/project/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/project/project4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Difference between static and dynamic websites?</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description> Static Sites:  collection of static web pages hard coded: the pages do not change, everybody gets the same page Cheap Fast Easy development Scalable Secure Version control of content: You can follow the changes of the content and the editor who changed and when it was done!  Dynamic sites:  dynamically generated More functions Easy management (CMS) Customized content Database storage (MySQL, Oracle… are not ideal for storing content) Only single upload Realtime updates (very important for E-commerce) slower - every webpage is built up on demand expensive  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Static Website Generator</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Static Website Generator (SWG) A Static Website Generator (SWG) is an item that helps building websites with little or no changes over time - so static websites. Before the SWGs came up static websites were generated by backend HTML programming. A dynamic website needs a CMS to be operated. SWGs try to combine the advantages of backend programming and CMS: Content creation via simple markup (often Markdown), no need to dig into HTML Separation of content and style(s) Support for well structured (textual) content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits vs. Drawbacks of Static Website Generators?</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description> Benefits  Building websites for static content (that doesn’t change regularly) Website Producer can focus on content instead of plain HTML because of a simple editing syntax Design can be done separately  Drawbacks:  Website Producer has to be at least a bit tech-savvy Maintenance is difficult No search capability - to find something you have to read through the page No user interaction  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is a Content Management System (CMS)?</title>
      <link>http://example.com/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Content Management System (CMS) A content management system (CMS) is a software application that can be used to manage the creation and modification of digital content without any coding. CMSs are typically used for enterprise content management (ECM) and web content management (WCM). ECM typically supports multiple users in a collaborative environment by integrating document management, digital asset management and record retention. Alternatively, WCM is the collaborative authoring for websites and may include text and embed graphics, photos, video, audio, maps and programme code that display content and interact with the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>All three of us started in autumn to study Content Strategy. Due to the learning block Backend Technology we have the chance to learn and try to create static website with help of hugo - a static Website Generator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>